

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Human centered design methodologies
Design thinking
User research methods
Agile methodology
Storytelling
Visual design
Prototyping
TML5
CSS3
Vuejs

TOOLS

Git

Paper, pen, stickies Whiteboard Figma, Adobe XD etc Jira, Confluence

PERSONAL SKILLS

Avid learner
Problem solver
Excellent communicator
Organised
Team player
Goal oriented

PORTFOLIO SITE

www.busayyyo.github.com

CONTACT

Phone: +49 15210186641 email: busayomioyewole@gmailcom

BUSAYO OYEWOLE

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

ABOUT

I am a user experience designer with background in psychology and frontend development. I've had experience designing interactive systems for a financial AI product and a B2B e-commerce service. I'm currently rounding up my masters degree in Usability Engineering and set to graduate in October 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

Siegwerk AG | Feb 2019 - Present Responsibilities include:

- Working closely with product owner on vision for product
- Employing the HCD process and methods to solve business problems
- Refining product based on new business requirements & user insights
- Visual design of user interface
- Communicating design solutions to developers and stakeholders
- Facilitating design sprint and workshops

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

FLAQSHIP GmbH | April 2018 - August 2018 Responsibilities included:

- Implementing UI designs using technologies such as HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript
- Testing and fixing websites for usability, functionality, crossbrowser compatibility and responsive issues
- Collaborating with other stakeholders to ensure userfacing features are well implemented

INTERACTION DESIGNER

Kudi Inc | June 2016 - September 2017 Responsibilties included:

- Conducting user and market research
- Crafting out bot-human experience for financial use cases
- UX writing of bot replies to suit designed contexts
- Conducting usability tests
- Working closely with developers and stakeholders to bring product to life

EDUCATION

MSC. USABILITY ENGINEERING

Rhine-waal university of applied sciences | 2017 - 2019 (set to graduate in October 2019)

MSC. PSYCHOLOGY

Obafemi Awolowo University | 2010 -2015 Upper Second-Class Honours